way went to a self
defense class . Yeah ,
Kicking a guy in the
crotch all morning really takes
it out of you .
Takes it out of you
. Now we can kick
anybody's ass after one class
. I don't think so
. What ? You want
to see me self defend
myself ? Go over there
and pretend you're sexual predator
. Go on . In
the area . Off course
, you could defend yourself
from an attack you know
is coming . That's not
enough . Look , I
studied karate for a long
, and there's a concept
you should really be familiar
with . It's what the
Japanese call who not G
is not a kind of
sushi . No , it's
a concept . It is
. It is . It's
freshwater healed . But maybe
it means that too .
Oh , I would kill
for a salmon skin roll
right now . Fine .
Get attacked . Only care
. Come on , Ross
, we're sorry . Please
tell us what it is
. Maggie is a state
of total awareness . Okay
? On Lee . By
achieving true Nagy , can
you be prepared for any
danger that may befall you
? You mean in case
someone's trying to steal your
bamboo sleeping matter ? Your
kettle of fish ? A
. What I'm saying is
it's one thing being prepared
for an attack against ,
like each other , a
whole another story being prepared
for an attack by surprise
. All right ? You
knew that was coming .
But that doesn't mean you
have you , Nagi .
Oh , you know what
? If we made reservations
, we could have a
nagging about 1/2 hour .
What's that ? A lesson
in the importance of unagi
. You're a freak .
Perhaps . Now I'm curious
. At what point during
those girlish screams , would
you have begun to kick
my ass ? All right
, so we weren't prepared
. I'm sorry . I
had to take such drastic
measures to make my point
, But I look ,
I just want you guys
to be safe . Uh
, not G seven skin
roll . Jack . Yeah
, Alex Trebek . Oh
, of course . Chuck
Woolery . Definitely . Phoebe
, you will not find
a single game show host
whose ass I cannot kick
. No , say it
. Say we are Nagy
. It's not something .
You are something you have
. Say it . You
know , I usually get
out of this , but
there's a chance you could
get very , very hurt
. No . Uh huh
. Nowhere to run .
I don't like sitting up
here . Are gonna go
. Rachel . They got
here first . Why's he
doing that ? Why is
he jumping on those women
? We should help them
. I don't think they